I used this skill on the goddess,
the minotaur, and bird-brain here...
I also charged my leather bag twice.
I'm out of MP now.
All I have is my natural MP outside
of these stat adjustments.
What happens if I consume all of that too?
Is that why I'm sweating so much?
This is bad.
I don't think my MP will last
until I reach the surface.
Paralyze!
It didn't work?!
You cannot apply the same skill
to a target repeatedly.
INFLICT SLEEP, SLEEP
S-Sleep!
SLEEP
So I can't spam the same skill
on the same target, huh?
Poison.
But it is possible
to stack multiple effects.
I'll bet there are other limitations, too.
Consuming my natural MP
must be getting to me...
You've got to be kidding me!
Fine.
I'll hit you guys with everything I have.
Let's see whether my MP gives out
or you all succumb
to my status ailments first!
RUINS OF DISPOSAL
Give me a break!
Just how many of these are there?
Paralyze! Paralyze! Paralyze! Paralyze!
I'm almost out of my own MP too.
Crap. I'm getting faint...
What the hell?
There's still more of you coming?
This is seriously getting bad.
All right.
Then...
let's just do this!
I can worry about it being the end
for me after I'm all dried up!
Paralyze!
Paralyze! Paralyze! Paralyze! Paralyze!
I guess I hit my mental limit first...
No, no, I've got at least one left in me.
Wring the stubbornness of a background
character for all it's worth,
Mimori Tou—
You have leveled up.
Your MP has been restored.
Paralyze!
Status adjustments increased.
- Paralyze! Paralyze! Paralyze!
- Wait, what?
- What just happened?
Why did I level up?
Oh, did I get experience
from the one that died?
A huge burst of it?
This means...
I can keep fighting now, right?
Paralyze!
Paralyze! Paralyze! Paralyze!
INFLICT PARALYSIS, PARALYZE / CONSUMES 10 MP
- Your skill has leveled up.
- Is that determined by
how many times I use it?
Does obtaining new skills
depend on leveling them?
Getting through this is my top priority now.
Hey, wait, what's this?
I can designate multiple targets at once now!
Paralyze!
That goddess might be the only one
my unique skill doesn't work on.
My success rate in the Ruins of Disposal
has been 100 percent!
There's no target mark
over the ones in the back...
So Inflict Status Ailment
has a limited range of effect?
Paralyze.
The same skill may cannot be
stacked multiple times.
Well, I kind of figured that would
be the case since I can't spam it.
Poison.
Poison. Poison.
INFLICT POISON, POISON
- Your skill has leveled up.
At this point...
These things all just look
like experience to me.
Stats: Open.
TOOKA MIMORI
- Seems like my stat adjustments
are multiplied by my level.
My starting MP was high,
and it's increasing dramatically.
My MP is my lifeline right now, though.
It's the fuel powering my unique skill.
If I run out of it,
then I'm completely finished.
TOOKA MIMORI
- You have leveled up.
You have leveled up.
Now then...
Sleep! Sleep! Sleep! Sleep! Sleep!
INFLICT SLEEP, SLEEP
- Your skill has leveled up.
- Now Sleep is level 2 as well.
You have leveled up.
There's no guarantee,
and I can't let my guard down,
but I think I can survive this.
With this power,
I can kill however many of them there are!
Looks like this is all that's still usable.
First, I need to escape from here.
I'll also need to find food and water.
A human killed by monsters...
Food...
Please give me food.
Cows and chickens?
My Poison skill has already worn off.
Ow! That's tough.
In that case...
Is their entire body made of acid?
God damn it.
This place was utterly meant
to destroy anyone thrown here.
Shit, I don't have any strength left...
But I need to get moving.
It changed color?
Oh man.
The purple part's getting bigger?
Damn it.
I'm not giving up!
It's heavy?! There's something inside?
That's good!
I don't know how it works,
and I don't know if it'll produce food again,
but I guess this is my paltry unique item?
Any second now.
You have leveled up.
- You have leveled up.
- What a grisly scene.
It looks like a massacre.
And here I committed this terrifying act
completely devoid of humanity.
TOOKA MIMORI
- You have leveled up.
What's this for?
...you.
...will... you.
One day... I will kill you.
I have to kill you, or I'll be killed...
Touka!
I'm sorry we kept you waiting.
It's all right now. Come with us, okay?
My aunt and uncle gave me normalcy.
They gave me the warmth of family.
They taught me kindness.
They empathized with the pain of others,
and I thought I had managed
to become like them.
Yet I feel nothing.
I'm not shaking in terror over taking a life.
My mind is unburdened by it.
I'm scaring myself.
That's just how it's gotta be.
Just accept who you are now!
You have leveled up.
Stats: Open.
TOOKA MIMORI
Yeah, I have to accept it.
I have to accept the new me,
the new Touka Mimori.
Paralyze. Poison.
You have leveled up.
The atmosphere here is awfully different.
This gem...
I guess I should pour magic into it?
Someone else disposed of
made it this far?
There are no signs of a struggle.
No food or water either.
Guess they decided
to welcome death together here.
That's kind of noble of you two.
Hmm? What's this?
Are these gems?
I might need this once I reach the surface.
Sorry, you two, but I'll be taking it.
I guess I'll check out the others.
This makes room number 25.
This one is taking away a lot
more of my MP than the others.
Were you disposed of as well?
Is this the wound that killed you?
Oh? I can read the language of this world.
My name is Anglin Bathard.
People call me Anglin the Great Sage.
However, some may know me
better by former name,
and that is...
"Anglin, the Hero of Darkness."
This is...
It's the same as that of the dark hero,
reputed to be the strongest of all.
The Goddess Vicius sent me here by force.
Apparently, I am no longer needed
and now considered an eyesore.
If you have the drive to make
it out of these ruins alive,
then I want to entrust you with something
I desperately brought this far.
At this rate, I suspect I will perish here...
Damn that goddess!
She said the Great Demon Empire was evil,
but she's far worse.
Though I guess I'm no different,
since I want revenge on her
and don't care about saving the world.
It's evil versus evil versus evil.
What an awful matchup.
This is... Forbidden Arts: Complete Works?
Are these recipes for medicine
and magic tools written in here?
Might prove useful later.
A scroll of forbidden magic?
I can't read it.
Forbidden magic, huh?
Well, a fabled sage went out of his way
to hide it and keep it with him.
I'm sure it must be a powerful spell.
If I can manage to decipher it,
maybe it'll be my ace in the hole
against that goddess.
Sorry, man.
Forgive me for trading mine with yours.
What's this?
"Beware the Soul Eater"?
"It's what killed everyone else"?
Looks like that's not opening
without something inside.
Does it lead to the surface, then?
That would mean...
It's here.
Somewhere close.
For certain.
Even the Hero of Darkness once
heralded as the strongest
couldn't defeat this monster
called the Soul Eater.
Stats: Open.
TOOKA MIMORI
I raised my level as much
as I could on the way here.
I just hope I can defeat it with my skill.
What is that?
A face?
Though that has to be what I need!
That thing's gotta be the Soul Eater.
Para—
That hurts!
Damn it!
It actually managed to stop me.
Its beam must activate the
moment I start intending to attack.
It doesn't leave any openings to attack.
What should I do?
I need that gem if I'm going to escape.
But killing this thing is way too tough.
I have to speak a skill name in
order to activate Inflict Status Ailment.
It has to be loud enough, too.
And this is as far as my range goes.
So what should I do?
Do I need to improve my stats even
more in order to break through?
No, I can't even activate my skill in
in the first place.
That means...
It came out on its damn own?
That thing managed to repel the
man once known as the strongest.
It's likely the reason for the zero
survival rate among the disposed.
There's no doubt that thing
rules these ruins.
So surely this is also
SOUL EATER
- my final fight for my life
in the Ruins of Disposal.
Ancient ruins...
I wonder if we'll be able
to wait them out here.
It's not doing anything?
It should know that
I'm lurking over here,
but it's not firing at me.
What is that?
Disgusting.
I get it.
This is a recreation.
It's showing me how the others
sent for disposal all died.
Their faces as it killed them...
Their final expressions before death.
It's showing me this
and watching how I react.
So this is how the Soul Eater amuses itself?
All the monsters here...
Every last one of them has vile-ass tastes!
This thing...
Paralyze!
Next I'll inflict Poison.
Damn it!
I can't do it!
Even though they're half dead already,
I-I can't do this to other people!
How could I ever use my horrific
Poison skill on another person?!
Screw this!
I...
I haven't fallen that low!
I'm not like you, using human souls as toys!
Monsters are one thing...
But against something that looks human?
They haven't done anything wrong!
How could I ever use Poison against them?!
I'm...
I'm still human!
S-Stay back!
Stop!
We're the same, aren't we?!
We're all human, right?!
Stay back!
That monster is enjoying my despair.
It's savoring it.
"I've found the ultimate prey."
That's what that face says.
It's enjoying this.
Stop!
Please stop it!
I'm begging you, s-stop!
Stay back!
Stay back! Stay back! Stay back!
Anyone, please...
Honestly, I'll take anyone!
Someone!
Someone please help me!
Somebody save me!
I can feel it.
The Soul Eater's ecstasy. Its emotion...
has peaked.
Paralyze.
Yeah, you peaked.
That was the best moment of your life.
The ultimate moment you'd been waiting for.
Which is why you let you guard down.
You didn't even realize it, did you?
That I never once lowered my left arm.
That's right.
It's the fatal flaw possessed of
those arrogant in their strength.
The moment you convince yourself
you're superior,
the moment you convince yourself
victory is inevitable,
gives rise to your greatest foe.
Overconfidence.
Your skill has leveled up.
INFLICT PARALYSIS, PARALYZE
- Your skill has leveled up.
That was all an act.
It was good, right?
Of course it would be.
For days, months, even years...
I tried to become harmless.
I tried to become normal.
I tried to become kind.
I even deceived and fooled myself
until I ultimately forgot
what I was really like.
Because I constantly had to keep
playing Mimori Touka,
the kind and normal background character.
Poison.
But all of them bore clear hostility.
Even if they were monsters you created
using the souls of those disposed,
there was no reason to hold back.
Meet hostility with hostility.
Meet bloodlust with the same, and crush them.
I had the weakest stats of all in these ruins.
And I'm glad of it.
Meant you all underestimated me.
That's why I survived.
A weak-ass human sent here for
disposal managed to get one over on you.
Pretty pathetic end for you, isn't it?
Don't you agree, Soul Eater?
So if they try and force themselves
to move while paralyzed,
it causes additional damage, huh?
Poison.
Your skill has leveled up.
INFLICT POISON, POISON
Enough.
Rest in peace.
Sleep.
You have leveled up.
Good job surviving.
I'm so happy for you!
You were incredible,
defeating that dragon zombie!
You really shocked me,
trying to eat that monster meat!
I hope our gems will prove
useful to you on the surface.
If they turn out to be cheap, sorry.
At any rate, thank you
for defeating the Soul Eater.
Please, get that goddess.
I'm under no obligation
to accept that request.
But don't you worry.
It might take me a fair deal of time,
but I absolutely plan to pay
that damn goddess back in the end.
Later.
ENCOUNTER ~AVENGER(S)~